Meet Bareng - a shared group wallet. One
account, one balance, and every member gets
their own spending limit. It feels like a
And this isn't a mockup. Seven real
transactions have already settled on-chain - a
shared spend, a DeFi deposit, an agent
Let's open it. Here's a shared pot: four
hundred and twenty dollars, held in one
Universal Account that works across Arbitrum,
Three members, each with a weekly limit. And
every limit is a real, owner-signed E I P
seventy-seven-oh-two grant - cryptography, not
Paying is simple. Pick a member, pay someone
by their handle - no addresses to copy - add a
note, and it settles on Arbitrum.
But nobody can overspend. Push past the cap,
and the button locks - over limit - blocked
before a single cent moves.
Every receipt in this feed is a real
settlement. Tap one, and it opens the actual
transaction on Arbiscan.
Topping up from another chain is one tap. This
is a ZeroDev Smart Routing Address - send USDC
from any chain, and it lands right in the pot.
Bareng also brings Indonesian money rituals
on-chain. Arisan - a rotating savings circle -
with a verifiable fair draw. The order comes
Split a bill, and Bareng nets who owes whom
down to the fewest possible transfers.
Receiving privately? Each payment lands on a
fresh, one-time stealth address, and the pot
quietly sweeps it in - completely unlinkable
A member's capped key can even become an A I
agent wallet. It pays per request over x
four-oh-two - signing a real payment the
Idle funds don't sit still. One tap supplies
them into Aave v three - the real
approve-and-supply batch - kept one tap away
The full story lives in the pitch deck, at
slash deck. Problem, solution, the seven
on-chain proofs, and why this wins. Bareng -